Kiem Hoang

Senior PHP Developer at BEAU VIETNAM., JSC

hoangkiem.ptit@gmail.com

Summary

All skill I got over 6 years experience about website developer, WordPress theme develop and something about Website develop as SEO on-page, SEO off-page, Server Linux. LAMP, LEMP...

And I'll continue learning more and more about the Web app, mobile application, IOT, Machine learning, Deep learning, Front-end develop, AI, Big data, Devops ...

Experience

Senior PHP Developer

March 2017 - Present

Continue of Beau Creative Vietnam (BEAU CREATIVE CO., LTD), and work as a developer.

Senior PHP Developer

June 2014 - March 2017 (2 years 10 months)

Start as the first full-time developer in this company, take care older outsource project and fix the products error, work with BeauTheme team. Start with zero of WordPress frontend skills. Some time work as a trainer, code team leader.

Professional Freelancer at NVC-Lighting

February 2013 - March 2016 (3 years 2 months)

Work as a developer, marketing consultant, and the Internet marketer, My job creates website http://nvc-lightingvn.com, http://thegioidenvn.com and SEO keywords to top 10.

Professional Freelancer

June 2012 - July 2015 (3 years 2 months)

Work as a freelancer, code backend, front end, create the website, project from this company.

Freelancer

August 2011 - July 2015 (4 years)

Just a small team work with PHP, SEO, Website support.

PHP Developer

September 2013 - June 2014 (10 months)

Work as PHP developer, SEOer, IT manager, Trainer, Customer support. The main job creates a social B2B network with China's team when finished planned & SEO keyword to top 10 Google.

PHP Developer

July 2011 - April 2012 (10 months)

First time work as PHP developer here, I learned many skills about, speaker, Backend Develop, Frontend develop, team work.

HTML, CSS, JS, jQuery, PSD to HTML, Teamwork

Education

Post and telecommunication institute of technology

Everage good, Information Technology, 2010 - 2013

Haiduong College of economics - technology

Good, Information Technology, 2007 - 2010

Kiem Hoang

Senior PHP Developer at BEAU VIETNAM., JSC

hoangkiem.ptit@gmail.com



Contact Kiem on LinkedIn